http://www.scottbrownrigg.com/privacy/

Privacy
What are you looking for?
MAP
Swipe :
/
Contact us
What are you looking for?
People
SB+C Architecture, D.P.C.
People
SB+C Architecture, D.P.C.
Digital Twin Unit
About
News
People
SB+C Architecture, D.P.C.
Privacy Policy
This website is owned and operated by Scott Brownrigg.
Scott Brownrigg is registered under registration number 02800215 and our registered office is at 77 Endell Street, London WC2H 9DZ
Introduction
Scott Brownrigg is committed to safeguarding the privacy of its website visitors and service users; this policy explains how your personal data is handled.
Scott Brownrigg will ask you to consent to the use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.
This website incorporates privacy controls which affect how your personal data is processed.
How we use your personal data
In this Section we have set out:
(a) the general categories of personal data that we may process;(b) the purposes for which we may process personal data; and(c) the legal bases of the processing
The Data, Purpose of Processing and Legal Basis
Scott Brownrigg may process data about your use of the website and services. The usage data may include your geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage data is an analytics tracking system. This usage data may be processed for the purposes of analysing the use of the website and services. The legal basis for this processing is legitimate interests, namely for monitoring and improving the website and the user experience.
On the website’s job application form, Scott Brownrigg may process your profile data including your name, address, telephone number, email address, current salary, educational details and employment details. The legal basis for this processing is consent.
Scott Brownrigg may process information contained in any job application enquiry you submit to us on the careers page. The enquiry data may be processed. The legal basis for this processing is consent.
Scott Brownrigg may process information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us ("correspondence data"). The correspondence data may include the communication content and metadata associated with the communication. The website will generate the metadata associated with communications made using the website contact forms. The correspondence data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you and record-keeping. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business and communications with users.
Your personal data will be strictly kept within Scott Brownrigg’s HR Department and with the person/s recruiting for that particular role. The Practice will not disclose your personal data to any person not directly associated with the role you are applying for or with any other companies within the Scott Brownrigg Group unless you have given permission for this to happen.
In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this Section, Scott Brownrigg may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.
Retaining and deleting personal data
This Section sets out Scott Brownrigg’s data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that compliance with legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal data. Personal data that is processed for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
Scott Brownrigg will retain and delete your personal data as follows:
(a) Personal data will be retained for a maximum of 2 years following your application, at the end of which period it will be deleted from the systems.
Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section, the Practice may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which Scott Brownrigg is subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.
AmendmentsScott Brownrigg may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on the website.You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy.
Your rights
You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not Scott Brownrigg processes your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information. That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, Scott Brownrigg will supply to you a copy of your personal data.
You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.
In some circumstances you have the right to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay. Those circumstances include: the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; you withdraw consent to consent-based processing. However, there are certain general exclusions of the right to erasure. Those general exclusions include where processing is necessary: for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.
In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, Scott Brownrigg will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.
To the extent that the legal basis for Scott Brownrigg processing your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.
You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us.
About cookies
A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.
Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.
Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user.
Scott Brownrigg uses cookies for the following purposes:
(a) Authentication – cookies are used to identify you when you visit Scott Brownrigg’s website and as you navigatethe website.(b) Analysis –cookies are used to help to analyse the use and performance of the website and services
Service providers use these cookies, which may be stored on your computer when you visit Scott Brownrigg’s website.
Scott Brownrigg uses Google Analytics to analyse the use of its website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to the website is used to create reports about its use. Google's privacy policy is available at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/
Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version.
Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.
If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on Scott Brownrigg’s website.
Concerns
If you have any concerns with the way in which we are gathering or using your personal data, please communicate any concerns with via the Contact page.
If you believe that your data protection rights have not been adhered to, you also have the right to raise concerns with the Information Commissioner’s Office at https://ico.org.uk/concerns/ or call 0303 123 1113.
You can contact Scott Brownrigg:
(a) by post, using the above postal address(b) by telephone, on the London contact number published on the website(c) by email, using the email address published on our website enquiries@scottbrownrigg.com
Changes to this Privacy Notice
This Privacy Notice may be changed by Scott Brownrigg at any time.
Let’s make
something extraordinary
You're looking
for exceptional architecture. We're looking for exceptional projects. Let's start a
conversation
Enquire
